Privacy Policy
==============

Intemodino Group s.r.o. ("Intemodino Group", "Intemodino", "We", and "us") is committed to protecting your privacy. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to describe to you our practices regarding the Personal Data we collect from users of (a) our website located at unitsmaster.com ("Site") and (b) Units Master application ("UnitsMaster", "App") owned by Intemodino and (c) services made available through the Site ("Services").  

#### Information Collection and Use

The term "Personal Data" as used in this Privacy Policy means information that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, as well as any other non-public information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing data.  
The term "Non-Personal Data" as used in this Privacy Policy means information that by itself cannot be used to identify or contact a specific individual in any way or form. Non-Personal Data may include log data, user IP addresses, browser types, domain names, and other anonymous statistical data. We collect Personal Data and Non-Personal Data, as described in the Privacy Policy.  
  
_Site_  
We do not collect or store any Personal Data except when you specifically provide it to us. You do not need any registration to visit our Site. You can visit the Site without giving us any information about yourself.  
If you contact us via e-mail or using the contact form, we will collect your name and e-mail address, as well as any other information included in the e-mail or contact form. By submitting the contact form or sending us an e-mail, you authorize us to use the provided information to respond to your requests or to aid us in serving you better. We use your Personal Data in some of the following ways:  
to optimize or improve our Site and App;  
to provide the Services and support you request;  
to send you administrative e-mail notifications, such as security or support and maintenance advisories;  
to respond to your inquiries related to employment opportunities or other requests;  
to detect, investigate, and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal.  
You may request that we delete your Personal Data any time, even before your request is fully resolved.  
  
_App_  
We do not process any orders. We do not collect and we do not have access to your payment details. All the App purchases will be processed by one of the following Data Processors: Apple Inc, Google Play, Microsoft, Amazon.  
  
Usage of Units Master allows you and your organization to fulfill the regulatory requirements of GDPR. We do not have access to (a) the information you enter into Units Master, this is only stored on your computer or your device and (b) data you sync via any third-party services. None of the information you enter into Units Master is transferred or synced to any of our servers.  
  
_Log Data_  
We collect Non-Personal Data when you visit our Site or use our Services. We gather and record information such as your browser type, operating system, your IP address, a date/time stamp for your visit, which pages of our Site you viewed and other statistics. This data is used to help us determine how much our visitors use specific parts of our Site and to estimate the total number of users visiting Site from specific countries or regions of the world. We may use the information we gather to understand our users base, analyze trends, administer the Site, improve the quality of our Site and Services.  
  
_Cookies_  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on some pages of our Site.  
Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our Site or other websites. Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to our Site and/or other websites on the Internet. Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) or users may opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).  
Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can set your browser to reject all cookies, accept cookies from certain websites only or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.  
  
_A Note About Children_  
We do not intentionally gather Personal Data from visitors who are under the age of 13. Our Site and Services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. If you are under the age of 13, per the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), do not use our Site and Services.  

#### Security of Your Personal Data

The security of your Personal Data is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the Personal Data, both during transmission and once we receive it. Unfortunately, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while Intemodino uses reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Data, We cannot guarantee its absolute security.  
  
_Information Sharing and Disclosure_  
We may share aggregated statistical information about users with advertisers, business partners, and other third parties. We do not share personal information that you may give us to any third-parties.  
  
Regardless of any choices you make regarding your Personal Data, We may disclose Personal Data if We believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary (a) in connection with any legal investigation (b) to comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on Intemodino (c) to protect or defend the rights or property of Intemodino or users of the Site, App and Services, and/or (d) to investigate or assist in preventing any violation or potential violation of the law, this Privacy Policy, our Terms of Use, or EULA.  

#### Links to other websites

Our Site may contains links to other websites owned by Intemodino Group and third-party websites which are outside the scope of this Privacy Policy. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies which you should read before you use these websites or submit any personal data. Intemodino Group is not responsible for the privacy practices of third-party websites and does not control the accuracy of information displayed by such websites.  

#### User Consent

By visiting our Site, using our Services, submitting Personal Data through our Site or Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy, and you represent and warrant that you have all rights necessary to submit such Personal Data.  

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. You can always check [this page](https://unitsmaster.com/privacy.html) for the latest version.  
  
Last updated on January 18, 2022  

Wednesday, September 18, 2024  

Copyright © 2024 Intemodino Group s.r.o.  
All rights reserved

Menu

×

Select your language

CS - Čeština  
  
DE - Deutsch  
  
DK - Dansk  
  
EL - Ελληνικά  

ES - Español  
  
FI - Suomi  
  
FR - Français  
  
IT - Italiano  

JP - 日本語  
  
KR - 한국어  
  
NL - Nederlands  
  
NO - Norsk (bokmål)  
  
PT - Português  
  
RU - Русский  
  
SV - Svenska  
  
TR - Türkçe  
  
ZH - 中文  

×
